So now that we have defined what Neural Networks are,
现在我们已经定义了什么是神经网络
we need to learn how to train them.
我们需要知道如何训练它们
Training them really means what parameter should they
训练它们实际上就是各边的权重应该是多少
have on the edges in order to model our data well.
这样才能很好地对数据建模
So in order to learn how to train them we need to look carefully at
为了学习如何训练它们 我们需要仔细研究
how they process the input to obtain an output.
它们如何处理输入来获得输出结果
So let's look at our Simple Neural Network, a Perceptron.
我们看看我们的简单神经网络 一个感知器
This perceptron receives a data point of the form x one x two,
这个感知器接收了 (x1,x2) 形式的数据点
where the label is y equals one.
标签是 y = 1
This means that the point is blue.
意味着这个点是蓝色的
Now the perceptron is defined by a linear equations
感知器由线性方程定义
say W one x one plus W two x two plus B,
例如 w1x1 + w2x2 + b
where w one and w two are the weights and the edges and b is the bias and the note.
其中 w1 和 w2 是权重（边） b 是偏差（节点）
Here w one is bigger than w two,
这里 w1 大于 w2
so we'll denote that by drawing the edge labeled w
我们表示为将用 w1 标记的边
one much thicker than the H labeled w two.
画的比用 w2 标记的边粗很多
Now with the Perceptor dots is it plots to point x one
感知器画出点 (x1,x2)
x two and it out to the probability that the point is blue.
并输出点是蓝色的概率
Here is the point is in the red area than the output is a small number,
对于这个红色区域的点 输出是个很小的数字
since the point is not very likely to be blue.
因为这个点不太可能是蓝色
This process is known as Feedforward.
这个流程叫做前向反馈
We can see that this is a bad model because the point is actually blue,
我们可以看出这个模型不好 因为这个点实际上是蓝色的
given that the third coordinate,
依据是第三个坐标
the Y, is one.
y 是 1
Now if we have a more complicated neural network then the process is the same.
如果我们有更复杂的神经网络 其实流程是一样的
Here we have thick edges corresponding to
粗边对应的是大的权重
large weights and thin edges corresponding to small weights.
细边对应的是小的权重
And the Neural Network plots the point in the top graph and also in the bottom graph.
神经网络在上下图表中都绘出这个点
And the outputs coming out will be a small number from the top model.
得出的结果是顶部模型的小数字
Then the point lies in the red area which means it has a small probability of being
那么这个位于红色区域的点是蓝色的概率很小
blue and a large number from the second model.
从第二个模型得出一个大的数字
So the point lights in the blue area which means it
点在蓝色区域 意味着
has a large probability of being blue.
它是蓝色的概率很大
Now as the two models get combined into this
这两个模型结合为
non-linear model and the output layer just blots
这个非线性模型
the point and it tells the probability that the point is blue.
输出层绘出这个点 告诉我们是蓝色的概率
As you can see, this is a bad model because it
可以看出 这个模型不好
puts a point in the red area and the point is blue.
因为它将点绘在红色区域 但是点是蓝色
Again, this process is called Feedforward and we'll look at it more carefully.
再强调下 这个流程叫做前向反馈 我们将仔细研究这一概念
Here we have our neural network in the other notations.
这是另一种标记法的神经网络
So the bias is in the outside.
偏差在外面
Now we have a matrix of weights.
现在有了权重矩阵
The matrix W superscript one denoting the first layer.
矩阵 W(1) 表示第一层级
And the entries are the weights W one one up to W three to.
条目是从权重 W11 到 W32
Notice that the biases have now be written as W three one and W three two.
注意 现在偏差写成了 W31 和 W32
This is just for convenience.
这只是为了方便
Now in the next layer we also have a matrix.
下一层级依然有一个矩阵
This one is W superscript two for the second layer.
W(2) 表示第二层级
This layer contains the weights that tell us how to combine
这一层级包含的权重告诉我们
the linear models in the first layer to obtain the non linear model in the second layer.
如何将第一层级的线性模型组合成第二层级的非线性模型
Now what happens is some math.
其中用到了一些数学知识
We have the input in the form X one X two one,
输入是 x1 x2 的形式
where the one comes from the bias unit.
1 是偏置单元
Now we multiply it by the Matrix W one to get these outputs.
我们将其与矩阵 W(1) 相乘 得出这些输出结果
Then we apply the sigmoid function to turn the outputs into values between zero and one.
然后应用 s 型函数 将输出变成 0 到 1 之间的值
Then, the vector from these values gets a one attached for the bias unit,
这些值形成的向量加上偏置单元 1
and multiplied by the second matrix.
与第二个矩阵相乘
This returns an output that now gets thrown into
对返回的输出应用 s 型函数
a sigmoid function to obtain the final output, which is Y hat.
获得最终结果 即 ŷ
Y hat is the prediction or the probability that the point is labeled blue.
ŷ 是预测 即点标为蓝色的概率
So, this is what Neural Networks do.
这就是神经网络的作用
They take the input vector and then apply
它们传入输入向量
a sequence of linear models and sigmoid functions.
应用线性模型序列和 s 型函数
These maps, when combined,
这些特征图相结合
become a highly nonlinear map.
变成高度非线性特征图
And the final formula is simply y hat equals sigmoid of W
最终公式是
two combined with sigmoid of W one applied to x.
ŷ = σW(2)*σW(1)(x)
And just for redundance,
再重复一遍
we do this again on a Multi-layer Perceptron or Neural Network.
我们在多层级感知器或神经网络上再来一遍
To calculate our prediction y hat,
要计算预测 ŷ
we start with the univector x,
我们从单位向量 x 开始
then we apply the first matrix and
然后应用第一个矩阵和 s 型函数
a sigmoid function to get the values in the second layer.
得出第二层级的值
Then we apply the second Matrix and
然后应用第二个矩阵和另一个 s 型函数
another sigmoid function to get the values on the third layer.
得出第三层级的值
And so on and so forth until we get our final prediction, y hat.
以此类推 直到得出最终预测 ŷ
And this is the Feedforward process that the Neural Networks
这就是神经网络从输入向量中
use to obtain the prediction from the imprint vector.
获得预测用到的前向反馈流程